First class honour (WAM: 85.94)

BIO

Software engineer with over 1 year of commercial experience in full-stack development, endeavouring to develop robost and performant solutions. Proficient in E2E web application design and development. Having strong team collaboration skills and a commitment to excellence, and flexible to different tech stacks and work environments.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (Computer Science)

2019 - 2022

The University of New South Wales (UNSW)

Featured high distinction courses:

- Advanced C++ Programming
- Algorithms and Programming Techniques
- Operating Systems

- Object-oriented Design and Programming (OOP)
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Database System

WORK EXPERIENCE

Backend Engineer

JAN 2024 - PRESENT

Australia Career Forum (ACF) - https://australiacareerforum.com/

- Involved in complete Software Development Life Cycle including system analysis, design and development.
- Contributed in external API/SDK integration, including Stripe, AWS SES, Discord and email template engine.
- Extensive experience of Xunit and Moq testing framework to provide full test coverage for code correctness.
- Managed production deployment on AWS EC2 cloud service, and setup resource monitor and alerts on Slack.
- Optimised makefile and dockerfile to create an automated one-click Linux dev environment setup process.

Tech stacks: C#, ASP.Net, Entity Framework Core, Xunit, Moq, Mysql, GraphQL, Docker, Jenkins, GitHub, AWS.

Full Stack Software Engineer

JAN 2023 - AUG 2023

Buka Australia Pty Ltd (Bukalapak) - https://about.bukalapak.com/en/about-us/

- Contributed in building gRPC and RESTful APIs by implementing tickets with more than 100 story points.
- Setup over 50 automated integration test with Jest test framework for both front-end and back-end services.
- Design and implemented a K8s Cronjob execution to run routine loan data integrity check.
- Troubleshooted loan circuit-breaker false-negative error and revised original design.
- Rescaled the GCP services with infrastructure as code (Terraform), which reduced running cost by around 33%.

Tech stacks: Golang, GoMock, PostgreSQL, Jest, TypeScript(Nuxt.js), HTML, Tailwind CSS, Docker, Kubernetes, Helm Charts, GCP, Oauth 2.0, Figma, Datadog, Gitlab CI/CD, Ubuntu.

PROJECTS

Movie Geeks - Web Application

University capstone project

Github repository: https://github.com/solaris-he/capstone-project-3900-f14a-moviegeeks-public

- Fully owned End-To-End SDLC from user stories analysis to system deployment and maintenance.
- Contributed in both front-end and back-end services including user profile management and movie recommendation.
- Designed 3NF form relational database schema to minimise redundancy, and setup SQL Server on GCP.
- Integrated Google Firebase into the application to leverage easy and secure user account management.

Tech stacks: Python, FastAPI, Sqlite3, Javascript, React.js, HTML, CSS, Google Cloud Platform, Google Firebase,

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front-end	Back-end	DevOps	2D/3D Graphic	OS & Tools
Next.js (React.js)	C# (ASP.Net)	GitHub	Figma	Linux (Debian-based)
Nuxt.js (Vue.js)	Golang	Gitlab CI/CD	Adobe Photoshop	Linux (RedHat-based)
TypeScript	Python (FastAPI)	Docker	Adobe Premiere Pro	Windows
JavaScript	C++	Kubernetes	Blender	Visual Studio
HTML	MySQL	AWS EC2	Autodesk Maya	VsCode
Tailwind CSS	PostgreSQL	GCP	Zbrush	Vim

REFERENCE

Available upon request.